马上就要被拔了
浇点水
所以他们都退了
都没有一样是
只能喂鸡了
这个胡萝卜长得真不成功
对
其实还能再种久一点的
说实话
买点牛羊粉
这个也是一个
快乐学生
面对这种
晕了吗
蝗虫的季节要到了
都在底下应该挺多的
你看看现在地下吃
一网打尽准备
全部位肌
你看这个多少在这天哪
阴阴天其实还是用紫外线
♪ I wake up from the sunshine on my face ♪
♪ So dehydri ♪
♪ Don't know what to say ♪
We sleep when by your side that i do last night take this medical away
♪ Yesterday was supposed to be quiet ♪
哎呀be to myself and sadh
Until i wanna go my friend for my door
♪ They wanted me to go out for ♪
♪ We were dancing in the dark with a few things in life ♪
♪ Like we hide it ♪
♪ We were dancing in the dark ♪
When i go
Oh whoa
Oh oh whoa
oh oh我
♪ Oh no ♪
♪ What a good ♪
♪ Oh oh woah ♪
♪ Oh woah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
Every one that feels the same
I know i only got myself to d
我决定怎么说
♪ In ours felt like we hide it ♪
♪ All ♪
♪ We were dancing in the dark ♪
We are d in the dark with a f you
♪ And i ♪
♪ But like we ♪
♪ It all we were dancing in the dark ♪
♪ We were dancing in the dark ♪
♪ I've been thinking of ♪
♪ How to leave you ♪
♪ Just to leave your fans ♪
♪ I've been thinking about how to deceive you ♪
♪ To make you leave me fun ♪
♪ My spare you tells me that if you ♪
♪ Only a matter of time ♪
♪ And is my biggest fall ♪
♪ You know that ♪
♪ Be with the eyes ♪
♪ The way ♪
♪ I feel is gone ♪
♪ And get the destiny ♪
The way
♪ I feel close ♪
♪ So you completely ♪
♪ We'll get the best of me ♪
♪ I've been thinking a wai ♪
♪ Believe you ♪
♪ I've been thinking the way ♪
♪ I could free ♪
♪ Before it all gets burned ♪
看看这个背西瓜水
你长在草地上休息吧
怎么说他们什么都决定在这个地方长得好神奇
这个火鸡长这么大
没见过这么大的螃蟹
哎这个番茄有点恐怖
这个本来我觉得还挺大的
跟这个一比
可以找一个看看这个size difference
爱是啥意思
那我们可以走出钢板的户外
完全被挡上了
看这给我们个超大字
哇塞露出来
不然就降温
挖眼里最大的瓜要出现
顶天立地啊
这个瓜太重了
它已经成为了自己的结构之处了
你看1even possible
看这个词可以给这个傻瓜相比
我得关机了
有
这个是今天长的最大
说来有点惭愧
但是好像颗粒还是很饱满的
确实不是很多
而且还有些没有长出来的
可能
这杆已经已经死了
直接把它给拆了
就他这个杆现在还是还是青色的
说明他还在给他弄几养的
诶好像可以吃
来期待一下大瓜
♪ 你好 ♪